A Guide to the Minutes and Meeting Files of the Virginia State Board of Health, 1896-2003
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes and Meeting Files of the Virginia State Board of Health, 1896-2003
The Library of Virginia
34146 and 43045
14.9 cubic feet and 9 volumes
Virginia State Board of Health
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 34146 transferred by Robert Triebley, Commissioner's Office, Department of Health, 1500 East Main Street, Room 214, Richmond, Virginia, 5 May 1992.
Accession 43045 transferred by Douglas Harris, Office of the Commissioner, Department of Health, 109 Governor Street, 10th floor, Richmond, Virginia, 11 January 2007.
Historical Information
The Medical Society of Virginia, formed in 1870, sponsored a bill to create a State Board of Health and Vital Statistics to supervise sanitation matters and to prevent the spread of contagious diseases. This bill was enacted into law by the General Assembly on February 13, 1872, but no funding was provided the Board, which functioned intermittently until 1896. The General Assembly passed an act on March 3, 1896, establishing and funding the Board of Health. An act passed on March 7, 1900, created local boards of health in every country and city and gave the State Board authority over them.
The position of Commissioner of Health was established as the executive officer of the Board of Health by an act of the General Assembly passed on March 14, 1908. The State Government Reorganization Act passed by the General Assembly on April 18, 1927, created the Department of Health under the aegis of the State Board of Health. The Department serves as the administrative arm of the Board of Health under the supervision of the State Health Commissioner and is responsible to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources.
The mission of the State Board of Health is to "provide leadership in planning and policy development for the Commonwealth and the Virginia Department of Health to implement a coordinated, prevention-oriented program that promotes and protects the health of all Virginians. In addition, the Board serves as the primary advocate and representative of the citizens of the Commonwealth in achieving optimal health." The goals of the Board include prevention and control of chronic disease, reduction of disparities in health care, improvement of the state's public health infrastructure, and improvement in the health and well-being of all Virginians. The Board of Health's core functions are to review and promulgate regulations, advise the Governor on health-related issues, formulate policy, advocate health care reform, and to advance quality of life through improved health.
Scope and Content
Contains minutes and files pertaining to the meetings and other activities of the Virginia State Board of Health. This collection contains both bound and loose minutes, as well as agendas, administrative material, reports, and regulations regarding public health matters.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Minutes, 1896-2001
Series II. Meeting Files, 1985-2003
Contents List
- Series I. Minutes, 1896-2001., 9 volumes and .175 cubic feet of paper records. (Box 1, Volume 1-9)
  Contains bound and printed minutes from meetings of the Virginia State Board of Health and meetings of its Executive Committee. The minutes include lists of members present, reports, budget information and discussion of public health issues. Bound minutes are from Accession 34146. Paper minutes are from Accession 43045.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Minute Book, 1896-1898. (Volume 1)
  - Minute Book, 1908-1918. (Volume 2)
  - Minute Book, 1919-1924 May. (Volume 3)
  - Minute Book, 1924 July-1943 June. (Volume 4)
  - Minute Book, 1943 July-1962 May. (Volume 5)
  - Minute Book, 1962 September-1970 April. (Volume 6)
  - Minute Book, 1970 July-1976 June. (Volume 7)
  - Minute Book, 1976 September-1979 May. (Volume 8)
  - Minute Book, 1979 August-1982 June. (Volume 9)
  - Minutes, 1995. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series II. Meeting Files, 1985-2003. (Box 1A-42)
  Contains files associated with meetings of the Virginia State Board of Health. Each meeting usually has multiple folders associated with it. In many cases, a pre-meeting or "prep" folder is included. In some instances, the business meeting and the regular meeting have separate folders, in others the material is mixed together. Also included here are miscellaneous subject files that pertain to meeting topics or are somehow connected to a particular meeting. Often, these files contain lists of new Board members, reports, material regarding public health issues, and regulations that were up for discussion at a meeting. The Board meetings were held periodically, sometimes monthly, but more often quarterly. Sometimes the meetings lasted for two days, in other cases only one day. The meeting files usually contain an agenda, minutes from the previous meeting, as well as copies of hand-outs and other materials for use during the session.
  Meeting files are arranged chronologically; miscellaneous subject files are arranged by according to year and then alphabetically within the year.
  - Pre-1991 Files.
    - Old Board Information, 1985-1990. (Box 1A, Folder 1)
    - Orientation Package, 1989. (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Reports on Boards and Appointments, 1990. (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - 1991 Files.
    - Board and Council Vacancies. (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of Public Need Regulations. (Box 1A, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 1A, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, April 24-25 (Prep file). (Box 1A, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 24-25 (Prep file). (Box 1A, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, April 24-25. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 24-25. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 24-25. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, April 24-25. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Mailings, May. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Mailings, June. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, June 20-21 (Prep file). (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, June 20-21 (Prep file). (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, June 20-21 (Prep file). (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, June 20-21. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, June 20-21. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, June 20-21. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, June 20-21. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, June 20-21. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, September 17-18 (Prep file). (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, September 17-18. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, September 17-18. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, September 17-18. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, October 29-30 (Prep file). (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, October 29-30. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, October 29-30. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 29-30. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October 29-30. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, December 12-13. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, December 12-13 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, December 12-13 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, December 12-13 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, December 12-13 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Files.
    - Boards, Commissions and Members. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, January 27-29. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, January 27-29. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, January 28 (Legislative Day Packet). (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 12-14. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 12-14. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 12-14. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, April 12-14. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, June 9-10. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Mailings, September. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 26-27. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October 26-27. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, October 26-27. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, October 26-27. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, October 26-27. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, December 10-11. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, December 10-11. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, December 10-11. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, December 10-11. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, December 10-11. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Mailings (various) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Legislation Related to Emergency Medical Services Do Not Resuscitate Program. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1993 Files.
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, January 26 (Legislative Day Visits). (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, April 26 (Teleconference). (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, June 21-22. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, June 21-22. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, June 21-22. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, June 21-22. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, June 21-22. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, August 22-24. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, August 22-24. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, August 22-24. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, November 11-12. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, November 11-12. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, November 11-12. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 11-12 (Retreat binder). (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 11-12 (Business meeting binder). (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Mailings, December. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, December 13-14. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, December 13-14. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, December 13-14. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, December 13-14. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Waterworks Regulations. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Waterworks Regulations. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1994 Files.
    - Meeting, February 2-3. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, April 21-22. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, April 21-22. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 21-22. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 21-22. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 21-22. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, June 6-7. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, June 6-7. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, June 6-7. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, June 6-7. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, September 8-9. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, September 8-9. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, September 8-9. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, September 8-9. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 20-21. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October 20-21. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, October 20-21. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, December 1-2. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, December 1-2. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1995 Files.
    - Board Members, 1995-1996. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, March 30-31. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, March 30-31. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, March 30-31. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, March 30-31. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, March 30-31. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, June 1-2. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, June 1-2. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, September 14-15. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, November 9-10. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 9-10. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1996 Files.
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, March 21-22. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, March 21-22. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, March 21-22. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, May 9-10. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, May 9-10. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, May 9-10. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, August 22-23. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, August 22-23. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, August 22-23. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 14-15. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Regulations. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Request from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1997 Files.
    - Bylaws. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, January 24-25. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 24-25. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, January 24-25. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, April 17-18. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 17-18. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 17-18. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, April 17-18. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, August 14-15. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, August 14-15. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, August 14-15. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, August 14-15. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, August 14-15. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 22-23. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1998 Files.
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, January 29-30. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, May 21-22. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, May 21-22. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, May 21-22. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, May 21-22. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, May 21-22. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Meeting (Executive Committee), July 9. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, September 10-11. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, November 12-13. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Memorandums and Correspondence. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1999 Files.
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, January 28-29. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 29-30. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, July 22-23. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 4-5. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 4-5. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, November 4-5. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Memorandums and Correspondence. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Memorandums and Correspondence. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2000 Files.
    - Meeting, February 3-4. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, February 3-4. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, April 27-28. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, April 27-28. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, August 10-11. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 2-3. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, November 2-3. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Memorandums and Correspondence. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 2001 Files.
    - Center for Quality Health Care Services and Consumer Protection, Request for Applications for Nursing Facility Beds. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Executive Summary: Repeal Existing Regulations Governinng Restaurants. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Joint Commission on Health Care (May-December). (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Joint Commission on Health Care (May-December). (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Joint Commission on Health Care (May-December). (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Evaluation. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, February 9. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, February 9. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, February 9. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, May 3-4. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, August 2-3. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October-November. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, November 2. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, November 2. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, November 2. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Files.
    - Meeting, February 8. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, February 8. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, February 8. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, April 25-26. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, April 25-26. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, April 25-26. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, April 25-26. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, April-May (Signed Minutes). (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, May. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, May 24. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, May (Electronic Mail in Preparation for Meeting). (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, May (Public Notice for Meeting). (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, June (Materials in Reponse to Meeting). (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, June (Materials Sent in Response to Meeting). (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, June-July. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, July 25-26. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, October 24-25. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Memorandum to Board Members. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - New Members. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Office of Health Policy and Planning Agenda. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Reportable Disease Surveillance in Virginia, 2000. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Reportable Disease Surveillance in Virginia, 2000. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - State Board of Health Meetings, 1998-2000. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - 2003 Files.
    - Meeting, January 31. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, January 31. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, January 31. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, January 31. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, January 31. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, April 25. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, April 25. (Box 42, Folder 6)